{
    "subject": "resource/Riola",
    "predicate": "property/areaCodeType",
    "object": "resource/Telephone_numbers_in_Spain",
    "human_readable": "The area code type of Riola is Telephone numbers in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9715316891670227,
            "question": "Is Riola an area code type in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8720571994781494,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Riola and Telephone numbers in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.848924994468689,
            "question": "Where are telephone numbers with the Riola area code used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8289968967437744,
            "question": "Are there any other area codes in Spain besides Riola?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8026896715164185,
            "question": "What kind of numbers does the area code for Riola identify?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7445802688598633,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a telephone number with the Riola area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7216994762420654,
            "question": "Is there a specific region associated with the Riola area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5893964171409607,
            "question": "How are area codes organized in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.561627209186554,
            "question": "What is the purpose of an area code like Riola?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45955410599708557,
            "question": "What information can you learn from an area code like Riola?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The area code type of Riola is Telephone numbers in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_262_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of an area code like Riola?",
            "html": "dbpedia_262_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How are area codes organized in Spain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_262_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a specific region associated with the Riola area code?",
            "html": "dbpedia_262_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_262_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions Riola being located in Spain and uses \"zip code\" as the identifier for locations, not a telephone area code. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention anything about telephone numbers or the type of area codes for Riola. They only discuss PIN codes (Postal Index Numbers) and their usage in Italy, and later mention that Riola is actually located in Spain and its correct location is Valencia, not Bologna district in Emilia-Romagna state of Italy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention any information related to the telephone area codes or types for Riola, which are specifically inquired about. Therefore, based on the given documents, the statement cannot be supported as true."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Riola is not located in Spain but in Italy. Hence, the area code type of Riola would be Postal Codes (PIN Code) in Italy and not Telephone numbers in Spain.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}